原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     送命題王賽太公  貓中之王  油膩希
校對     數數這集多少啪意詞賽
后期      灰灰是菇涼      時間軸    加森
總監     新浪微博@賽太公
生
活
大
爆
炸
第十二季  第一集
《生活大爆炸》前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
你能相信我們的小羊羔終于要嫁人了嗎
Can you believe our little lamb is finally getting married?
他肯定不信
He can't believe it.
我也不敢相信
And neither can I.
爸  你還好嗎
‭Hi, Dad. How you doing?
我以"連你都能證婚網"
Then by the power vested in me...
所賦予我的合法權利
by EvenYouCanPerformWeddings.Com...
我現在宣布你們正式結為合法夫妻
...I now pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
時至今日
早安啊  老婆
Good morning, wife.
早安啊  老公
Good morning, husband.
真不敢相信我們真的結婚了
I can't believe we're actually married.
正式完婚了  根據傳統
It's official. According to tradition,
我們應該把床單掛在外面
we should hang the bedsheets outside
這樣其他村民就能知道我們行房了
so the villagers can see that we consummated.
我覺得這有點不太合適吧
I don't think that that's appropriate,
畢竟我們是在這里開始我們的蜜月之旅
considering where we're starting our honeymoon.
你說的有道理
Well, I suppose you're right.
樂高樂園
不過如果你仔細想想
Although, when you think about it,
樂高有著形容夫妻房事的最完美隱喻呢
Lego is the perfect metaphor for marital congress.
兩片樂高"合體"并帶有爽度十足的咔噠聲
Two pieces that interlock with a satisfying snap.
原來你當時發出的聲音是這意思啊
Oh, that's the sound you were making.
我差點就忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
在你睡覺的時候  我點了客房送餐
While you were sleeping, I ordered room service.
真的嗎
Really?
請看
Voila!
你本來還以為是食物  對吧
You thought it was going to be food, didn't you?
謝爾頓跟艾米出去度蜜月你們是不是很爽啊
Is it nice having Sheldon and Amy away on their honeymoon?
是啊  因為我跟萊納德有大把的獨處時間
Yeah, because now Leonard and I get all this alone time.
但你倆不能獨處啊  我們在呢
But you're not alone. We're here.
是啊  你們在呢...
Yes. Yes, you are.
需要我們先行告退  好讓你們夫婦有空聊
Would you like us to leave so you and Leonard can talk about
你們之間有的共同話題嗎
all the things you have in common?
哈哈哈  吹牛被抓到了吧
Ha, ha, she called your bluff.
有件很酷的事情跟你們分享
So, something pretty cool happened.
第3頻道邀請我去上明晚的新聞
Channel 3 asked me to be on the news tomorrow night
去聊聊即將到來的流星雨
to talk about the meteor shower.
-那很棒啊  -恭喜你啊
- Oh, that's great. ‭- Hey! ‭Congratulations.
尼爾·德格拉斯·泰森也是這么開始火的
You know, that's how Neil deGrasse Tyson got his start.
美國知名天文學家  常上電視節目科普
算是天文科普界的紅人  也是海頓天象館的館長
他從在海頓天象館就職
He went from the Hayden Planetarium
到去地方電視臺當嘉賓
to guesting on the local news
最后在網上吐槽毀了大家所鐘愛的電影
to ruining everyone's favorite movies on the Internet.
他曾吐槽電影《泰坦尼克號》中的星空與真實情況不符
導致導演在10周年紀念DVD中修改了星空
現在這機遇輪到我身上了
Now it's happening to me.
或許我該開始列個表
Ooh, I should probably make a list
寫下歌舞電影《媽媽咪呀2》中的科學不合理處
of all the scientific inaccuracies in Mamma Mia 2.
你確定要在電視直播中承認你看過這個電影嗎
You're gonna go on live TV and admit you've seen that movie?
是你老公帶我去看的
Hey, your husband's the one who took me.
影后梅麗爾·斯特里普與雪兒  小爺看過咋的
Meryl Streep and Cher? Yeah, I saw it.
聽起來像里面有人啊
Sounds like someone's in there.
天啊  有人進去偷謝爾頓與艾米家可怎么辦
My God, what if Sheldon and Amy are getting robbed?
還可能更慘  是他們提早回來了
Or worse, what if they're back early?
沒回來  他們剛剛發了一張
They're not; they just posted a picture
在自由女神像前的合影
in front of the Statue of Liberty.
-真的那尊還是樂高  -樂高
- Real or Lego? ‭- Lego.
我們該怎么做  我們誰去看看情況嗎
So, what should we do? Should someone go check it out?
我愿意  但我明天得上電視
I would, but I got to be on TV tomorrow.
我得保護好我的生財機器啊
Got to protect the money.
是的  里面絕對有人
Oh, yeah, someone's definitely in there.
好  大伙先進我們的公寓
Okay, let's go into our apartment.
我們把門鎖上  再打給警...
We'll lock the door, we'll call the pol...
有人在里面嗎
Hello?! Anyone in there?!
-有事嗎  -是福勒先生啊
- Yes? - ‭Oh, uh, Mr. Fowler.
抱歉  我們不知道你在這里
Sorry, we didn't know you were here.
我們還以為是有人偷闖入了他們家里
We-we actually thought someone was breaking in.
而你當時準備好要放倒賊人了
And we were ready to take them down.
艾米請我來給她的植物澆水
Amy asked me to water her plants.
她沒養植物
She doesn't have any plants.
好吧  被你抓到我撒謊了
Well, you caught me in a lie.
在下告辭
Have a good day.
剛才很奇怪吧
That was weird, right?
怪嗎  我已經失去分辨怪的能力了
Was it? I-I honestly can't tell anymore.
你有看過《媽媽咪呀》第一部嗎
Hey, did you even see Mamma Mia 1?
不需要  這續集能自成一部
Didn't need to. The sequel stands on its own.
來
Here you go.
如果兩位游覽紐約時需要任何事物的推薦
If you need any recommendations while visiting New York,
隨時歡迎你們聯系我
please don't hesitate to contact me.
我們正在度蜜月
Well, it is our honeymoon.
所以我們會挺忙的
So we are going to be quite busy.
懂了
Got it.
要去看哈利波特舞臺劇  上下兩部
Harry Potter play, parts one and two.
而明天我們要去參觀
And tomorrow, a tour of the sites
尼古拉·特斯拉居住  工作與慢慢發瘋的地方
where Nikola Tesla lived, worked and slowly went crazy.
當然不用說  還有交媾
And, of course, coitus.
那祝兩位享受紐約之旅  以及...享受交媾
Well, enjoy New York. And, I guess, coitus.
真的假的  謝爾頓
Really, Sheldon?
你想再來一發嗎
You want to do it again?
別一副很驚訝的樣子好嗎
Don't act surprised.
明明白白寫在日程表上了
It's clearly marked on the schedule.
我看看
Now,
我們是應該先熨平我們巫師袍上的褶皺
shall we steam the wrinkles out of our wizard robes,
還是做一次激情并受社會認可的愛
or make vigorous, socially sanctioned love?
任何一種我都能消掉一項待辦事物
Either way, I can check something off my to-do list.
社會認...  哇靠  還真的寫了
Socially sanc-- Oh, wow. Yeah, there it is right there.
快點  馬上輪到拉杰了
Uh, hurry. Raj is on next.
我真不敢相信他們砍了電視劇《吸血鬼日記》
All right. I can't believe they canceled Vampire Diaries
卻留著這破爛節目
but they'll show this.
這可是新聞啊
This is the news.
那劇是在說一個女人為兩個帥壯吸血鬼左右為難
And that was a woman torn between two hunky vampires.
你的點是什么
What is your point?
拉里  我知道你在里面
Larry? I know you're in there!
是艾米她媽媽嗎
Is that Amy's mom?
讓我進
Let me in.
讓  我  進
Let me in!
不是她媽就是來吃小豬的大壞狼
Either that or the Big Bad Wolf.
拉里
Larry?
福勒太太  你有什么事嗎
Mrs. Fowler, are you okay?
我沒事  你該擔心要出事的是我老公
Oh, I'm okay. It's my husband you should worry about.
我們有替他擔心
Oh, we do.
拉里  快開門
Larry, come on.
我覺得他應該不在里面
I don't think he's in there.
他當時來澆過不存在的植物
I mean, he came by to water the imaginary plants,
但后來他就走了
but then he left.
好傻好天真
You are so naive.
金發妹能把你生吞活剝吃干抹凈  再吐出來
Blondie here is gonna chew you up and spit you out.
你別告訴他嘛
Well, don't tell him.
快點  你們有備份鑰匙  把門打開
Come on, you have an extra key. Open it up.
好吧  但我告訴你
All right, but I'm telling you
他不在里面
he's not in there.
你看  沒人吧
There. See?
他絕對在這里
Oh, he's in here.
我能聞到他的斧牌身體芳香噴霧
I can smell his Axe body spray.
他用斧牌身體芳香噴霧呢
He wears Axe body spray.
你高興了吧  你聞起來像艾米她老爸
You happy? You smell like Amy's dad.
拉里  快跟去看
Larry? ‭Ooh, come on.
我們不應該少管閑事嗎
Ah, shouldn't we mind our own business?
有時候真感覺你完全不了解我
Wow, sometimes it's like you don't know me at all.
看到沒  他不在這里
See, he's not here.
你可沒有我了解他
You don't know him like I do.
老實說  我們對你倆都不了解
To be fair, we don't know either of you.
滿意了吧
Satisfied?
對  我現在聞到他了
Oh, yeah, now I smell him.
天  這個天氣預報女孩可真辣
Man, that is one hot weather girl.
憑什么我說這種話就得送命
How come if I say that I get in trouble?
你想說嗎  你可以說呀
You want to say it? You can say it.
你想得美
Nice try.
今晚你得用其他的理由
You're gonna have to find some other way
來拒絕和我滾床單了
to not have sex with me tonight.
這不是天氣預報女孩   這是天氣預報女郎
And it's not weather girl, it's weather woman.
今天來給我們講解
And with us today to talk about
流星雨和最佳觀測地點的人是
the upcoming meteor shower and the best places to view it,
加州理工天體物理學家  拉杰什·庫薩帕里博士
Caltech astrophysicist Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali.
-感謝您的蒞臨  -感謝邀請
- Thank you for being here. - Thank you for having me.
我猜你們是沒請到尼爾·德格拉斯·泰森吧
I guess Neil deGrasse Tyson was unavailable.
沒錯
Yeah.
你說"沒錯"是什么意思
What do you mean, "Yeah"?
不是重點
Not important.
所以  這場流星雨的最大看點是什么
So, what can we expect to see from this meteor shower?
肯定會有很多可燃氣體接踵而來
Well, I think you can count on a lot of flaming gas,
如果你的首選之人
which is what you would have gotten
尼爾·德格拉斯·泰森有來  也會有很多[放屁]
from your first choice, Neil deGrasse Tyson.
停下來  拉杰  快剎車啊
Pull up, Raj, pull up!
聽起來你和泰森博士之間沒什么愛呀
Sounds like there's no love lost between you and Dr. Tyson.
不不  我可愛尼爾了
Oh, no, I love Neil.
雖然不如尼爾自戀  但誰能比得上呢
I mean, not as much as Neil loves Neil, but who does, right?
簡直不忍直視  但我眼睛舍不得轉
I want to look away, but I can't.
導播說我們已經超出時間了
Oh, you know, I'm told we are out of time,
流星雨一點沒認識到
having learned nothing about meteor showers
但對庫薩帕里博士卻了解了太多
and too much about Dr. Koothrappali.
謝謝收看
Thank you.
你知道我最愛百老匯劇場的哪一點嗎
Do you know what I love about Broadway theater?
就是那種互動的感覺
It's so interactive.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
你離演員這么近  仿佛自己就融入了戲劇中
You're so close to the actors. It's like you're in the play.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
如果你喊一聲"哈里  小心呀"
I mean, you yell, "Harry, watch out,"
他就會看向你
he looks right at you.
不光是哈里  臺上每個人都盯著我呢
And not just Harry, everyone onstage.
雖然可能會顯多余  嗯哼
At the risk of sounding redundant, uh-huh.
好了  天色已晚
All right, well, it's a bit late,
不過我已經留出今晚的余下時間
but I did block out the rest of the evening
來履行我們的"夫妻之實"
for conjugal relations.
我們該洗澡嗎
Should we shower?
我是說開始之前  不是中途
I mean before, not during.
人們就是這么滑倒摔破髖骨的
That's how you fall and break a hip.
我還在倒時差中
You know, I'm a little jet-laggy.
早上再說吧
Maybe we can revisit this in the morning.
不行  如果今晚不做
Oh, no can do. If we miss tonight,
就得等到周四的6點才能做了
it's not scheduled until Thursday at 6:00.
而且那場得是無前后戲的"快版"
And that'll have to be "No frills,"
因為我們6點半還訂了紅花鐵板燒的座呢
'cause we've got a 6:30 reservation at Benihana.
謝爾頓  我們必須要按時間表來做這事嗎
Sheldon, do we really have to do this on a schedule?
你是提議我們隨性而為嗎
Are you suggesting spontaneity?
我想是的
I-I guess, yeah.
所以因為我們結婚了  就可能隨時滾床單了嗎
So, now that we're married, sex can occur at any time?
比如  我倆正刷牙呢
Like, we can be brushing our teeth,
突然你那薄荷味的舌頭就伸進了我嘴里
and suddenly your minty-fresh tongue is in my mouth?
不  還是算了
No, thank you.
真的嗎  偶爾隨性地"炒飯"也不行嗎
Really? Would it be so bad to mix it up a little?
還炒飯呢  你誰啊  妙廚貝蒂[食品品牌]嗎
Mix it up? Who are you, Betty Crocker?
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
去洗澡
Uh, to take a shower.
既然現在我們隨時都可能滾床單
Now that sex can happen at any time,
那我就要時時做好準備
I always have to be ready.
我們不如住在瀑布底下吧
Should probably live under a waterfall.
你不用擔心今晚的份了
Well, you don't have to worry about sex happening tonight.
謝謝  不過我還是要去沖一沖
Well, thanks, but I'm still gonna rinse off.
我今天在禮品店碰了不少東西呢
I touched a lot of stuff in the gift shop.
沒有留信息  沒有留字條  誰會這么做
No message, no note. Who would do that?
什么樣的丈夫才會...
What kind of husband would...
如果你讓他說話  可能你就知道了
If you let him talk, maybe you'll find out.
好吧  拉里
Fine. Larry?
他說完了   無聲勝有聲
Well, there you go. What more can he say?
我們回家吧
Let's go home.
我想我還是留下吧
I think I'll stay.
如果你留下  那我也要留下
Well, if you're going to stay, then I'll stay.
好吧  你知道誰不必留下嗎
All right, well, you know who doesn't need to stay?
我們  快走吧
Us. Come on.
佩妮  快點
Penny, come on.
我覺得這兩人的婚姻不會長久啊
I don't think those two are gonna make it.
可憐的福勒先生  我真為他感到可憐
Poor Mr. Fowler, I really feel sorry for the little guy.
我知道  他們有了艾米后
I know. After they had Amy,
她就該把他吃掉算了
she should've just eaten him and been done with it.
看看你從自然節目中學到了不少啊
Look at you retaining facts from a nature show.
說真的  他到底看中了她什么呀
I know, really, what did he ever see in her?
他人這么和善  而她簡直是個潑婦
He's so, so sweet, and she's such a ballbuster.
有的男人覺得強悍的女人性感
Some guys think strong women are sexy.
可他們看起來也沒什么共同點呀
Yeah, but they seem to have nothing in common.
有時候異性才會相吸
Yeah, well, sometimes opposites attract.
等等  你是說我倆和他們一樣嗎
Wait, are-are you saying we are like them?
我不知道  有一點吧
I don't know, maybe a little.
所以你體貼又溫順  而我是艾米的老娘了
So you're the sweet, quiet one and I'm Amy's mom?
你是這個意思嗎
Is that what you're saying?
快看尼爾·德格拉斯·泰森剛才發了推特
Hey, check out what Neil deGrasse Tyson just tweeted.
"有人告訴我
"I've been informed that some random,
某個想出名的無名小卒
attention-seeking nobody
在本地新聞中無恥地攻擊我"
took a cheap shot at me on the local news."
是我耶  各位  他說的是我耶
That's me. Guys, he's talking about me!
看在你來自異國他鄉的份上
You know, I cut you a lot of slack
我一直對你優待有加
'cause you come from another country,
但你來美國也不是一天兩天了
but you've been here a long time.
拉杰  你應該向泰森博士道歉
Raj, you need to apologize to Dr. Tyson.
為什么  這對我有好處呀
Why? This could be good for me.
人人都愛看精彩的推特罵戰
Everybody loves a good Twitter feud.
水果姐凱蒂·佩里和霉霉泰勒·斯威夫特曾在推特互懟
尼爾和我可以成為新一代的
Neil and I could be like
水果姐和霉霉
the new, uh, Katy Perry and Taylor Swift.
拉杰  別這樣  你沒這么下作吧
Come on, Raj, you're better than this.
你肚子得留點空間吃甜點
Oh, leave room for dessert
因為我會讓你把說出來的話都吃回去
'cause I'm gonna make you eat those words.
"親愛的泰森博士
"Dear Dr. Tyson,
我就像上皮組織一般
much like epithelial tissue,
附在你的皮膚之下[讓你難受了]"
it appears I've gotten under your skin."
想摔手機耍帥
iPhone drop,
但不行  我沒有買蘋果保修服務
but I won't 'cause I don't have AppleCare.
他回了什么
‭What'd he say?
"加油啊  天才  皮膚本身就是上皮組織"
"Nice try, genius. The skin is epithelial tissue."
戰斗打響了
Oh, it's on.
他是水果姐  而我就是霉霉
He's Katy, I'm T-Swift.
你能怎么辦  他可是外國人
What are you gonna do? He's from another country.
這里就是特斯拉曾經
And here we have the former hotel where Tesla
完成三相交流電動機的前旅館
perfected the three-phase alternating current motor.
他說錯了  我得說點什么
That's wrong. I'm gonna say something.
別說
Don't.
不說大家怎么知道我是在場最聰明的孩子
Well, then how will everyone know I'm the smartest boy here?
你就別糾結了
Just let it go.
你沒什么事吧
Is everything all right?
感覺你今天早上挺暴躁的
You seem testy this morning.
我沒暴躁
I'm not testy.
那我只能相信你的話了
I'll have to take your word for it.
畢竟暴躁沒法測試
There's no test for testy.
你會不會是欲求不滿
Is it possible that you're sexually frustrated?
現在老娘真的暴躁了
Okay, now I'm testy.
如果你遵守我的交媾時間表
If you had adhered to my coital schedule,
現在你的大腦都漂浮在催產素的海洋里了
your brain would be floating on a sea of oxytocin right now.
別跟我聊我的大腦  我可是神經生物學家
Don't talk to me about my brain. I'm a neurobiologist.
那你就該知道大人給彼此的特殊抱抱
Then you should know the benefits of the special hug
能帶來什么好處
that grown-ups give each other.
謝爾頓  大家都在聽
Sheldon, everybody's listening.
他們當然在聽啦  我們這么有趣
Of course they're listening; we're interesting.
不像那位仁兄
Unlike that guy.
我要走了
I-I'm walking away from you.
我才剛結婚
I'm only recently married.
我該留在原地  還是追上去  說點有用的
Do I stay here? Do I follow? Say something useful.
早上好呀  小太陽
Morning, sunshine.
我看到你在煮濃縮咖啡
So I see you're making espresso.
是的
Yup.
需要額外充電
Just need that extra jolt
才能順利當一整天的潑婦啊
for a successful day of ballbusting.
是嗎  你好像不喝也能做到
Really? I don't, I don't think you do.
你把我們跟世間最奇葩的夫婦相提并論
You know, you compared us to the strangest couple we know,
他們可是比艾米和謝爾頓
and we know Amy and Sheldon,
霍華德和伯納黛特  拉杰和他的神經小狗還奇葩
Howard and Bernadette, Raj and his twitchy little dog.
抱歉  我不該那么說
I-I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
是因為那么說不好  還是因為那不是真的
Because it wasn't nice or because it wasn't true?
那不是真的
It's not true.
福勒太太是個易怒  報復心強的女人
Mrs. Fowler is an angry, vindictive woman,
而你是如此善良暖心  溫柔體貼
whereas you are warm and-and loving,
能快速寬恕別人的人
quick to forgive.
你少來
Oh, please.
我是認真的  再說我跟艾米的爸爸一點都不像
I-I'm serious. And I'm nothing like Amy's dad.
他就是個膽小如鼠  不敢捍衛自己的小男人
He's a mousy little man who can't stand up for himself.
我想說的是你不像她  所以我們不像他們
My point is you're not like her, so we're not like them.
三十年后  你會因為我很可怕
Well, 30 years from now, are you gonna hide from me
而躲起來嗎
because I'm so scary?
我不覺得你可怕啊
Hey, I-I don't think you're scary.
你突然動的時候我是會縮一下  但...
Yes, I flinch when you make sudden moves, but...
那更多反映的是我的童年問題  而不是你
...that says more about my childhood than you.
輪到你了
Your turn.
等等  我先看看尼爾有沒有
Hang on, I'm checking to see if Neil replied
回復我的怒懟
to my latest smackdown.
不是吧  你不覺得在推特上互懟很傻嗎
Really? Don't you think this Twitter feud is a little silly?
當然不會了
Absolutely not.
這是兩名備受尊敬的科學家
It's-it's two respected scientists
在公共論壇辯論相反觀點
debating opposing views in a public forum.
你叫他邁克·泰森的妹妹
You called him Mike Tyson's little sister.
美國著名拳王
是啊  現在邁克·泰森也生我氣了
Yeah, and now Mike Tyson's mad at me, too.
拉杰  你攻擊他并不會讓人欣賞你
Raj, you're not going to impress anyone by attacking him.
伯納黛特  你口氣好老人哦
Oh, Bernadette, you sound so old right now.
他說需要喘口氣  他受不了我了
He said he needs a break, and I'm too much for him.
那一定不是真心話
Oh. I'm sure he didn't mean that.
他說我超級霸道
He said I'm overbearing!
才不是呢  您只是霸道得剛剛好
Oh, please, you're just the right amount of bearing.
我知道他愛你
Look, I know he loves you.
你給他點空間  他一定會回家的
If you just give him some space, I'm sure he'll come back.
你真這么想
You really think so?
真的
Yeah, I do.
你是個好姑娘  佩妮
You're a good person, Penny.
希望我們能多多相處
I hope we get to spend lots of time together.
我也是
Me, too.
-什么事  -上路吧
- Yes? - ‭Hit the road.
-可是...  -立刻滾
- But... - ‭Now!
我能去拿我的行李嗎
Can I get my stuff?
趕緊地
Be quick about it! ‭
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hello.
我給你帶了兩個熱狗
I brought you two hot dogs.
你不吃一個嗎
A-Aren't you gonna eat one?
這可是從路邊攤買的  你瘋了嗎
From a street cart? Are you crazy?
我敢用手拿著都夠讓我佩服自己的了
I'm amazed that I'm holding them.
我不是很餓
I'm not really hungry.
你知道我是個不太喜歡肉體接觸的人吧
You realize that I'm not a particularly physical person.
-我知道  -我小的時候
- I know. - ‭When I was little,
別人問我長大想做什么時
and people asked me what I wanted to be when I grew up,
我總是回答"裝在罐子里的大腦"
I'd always say, "A brain in a jar."
好吧
Sure.
但我想當個好老公
Yeah, but I want to be a good husband to you,
而親密關系是其中一環
and intimacy is a part of that.
拜托你先把熱狗放下
Please put those down.
我就是擔心  如果我不安排
I'm just worried that if I don't schedule
床上運動的時間表  我可能根本就不會想起
our bedroom endeavors, then I may not think about them,
你就會變得冷漠疏遠
and you'll grow cold and distant
到肌肉發達的碼頭工人懷里尋找慰藉
and seek solace in the arms of a heavily-muscled longshoreman.
我上哪兒去找碼頭工人
Where would I find a longshoreman?
碼頭啊  寫得明明白白了
Along the shore. It's in the name.
謝爾頓  除了你  我無法跟其他男人相好
Sheldon, I could never be with anybody but you.
那我就安心了
That's good to know.
我可不想跟一個
I wouldn't want to fight a man
敢摸魚的勇士打架
who's brave enough to touch a fish.
我們互相退一步好不好
How's this for a compromise?
隨你安排時間表  別告訴我就行
Make all the schedules you want, just don't tell me about them.
太棒了
Excellent.
我會自己編寫一個能自動生成
I'll create an algorithm that'll generate
偽隨機時間表的算法  你知道
a pseudo-random schedule. Yeah, and do you know why
為什么不是真隨機時間表嗎
it won't be a true random schedule?
因為生成真隨機數字
Because the generation of true random numbers
在電腦科學領域仍是未解難題
remains an unsolved problem in computer science.
跟我來
Come with me.
-我們要去哪兒  -酒店房間
- Where are we going? - To the hotel room.
等我們到了  我要你再說一遍
And when we get there, I'm gonna need you
但你得脫光說
to say that again, except naked. ‭
本座庫博士
Go for Dr. K.
你是拉杰什·庫薩帕里嗎
Is this Rajesh Koothrappali?
我是  你是哪位
Yes. Who is this?
尼爾·德格拉斯·泰森
Neil deGrasse Tyson.
哎喲媽呀
Uh, w-wow.
推特上這樣玩挺有意思的吧
How fun is this Twitter thing, huh?
你覺得自己很好笑嗎
You think you're funny?
我沒有《宋飛正傳》那么好笑
I'm-I'm not Seinfeld funny,
但我做過一次開放麥脫口秀
but I did an open mic night once.
在酒吧舉行的民間脫口秀
任何人都可以上臺表演
你難笑到死
You're not funny.
笑笑屋酒吧的人就是這么說的
Yeah, that's what they said at the Chuckle Hut.
這樣好不好
How about this:
我下周在帕薩迪納的佛羅曼酒吧舉辦簽書會
I've got a book signing at Vroman's in Pasadena next week.
你來當我的面  說你在網上說的那些話怎么樣
Why don't you come by and say some of those things to my face.
不了不了
Oh, no,
不過謝謝邀請
but thanks for the invite.
算你機靈  下次你拿起電話時
Smart move, and the next time you pick up your phone,
記住  老子就是把冥王星踢出太陽系的人
remember, I'm the guy who kicked Pluto out of the solar system.
是冥王星活該  先生  謝謝  再見
And it deserved it, sir. Thank you. Bye-bye.
真有意思
Well, that was fun.
看看誰還需要德格拉斯式"修理"
Let's see who else needs a deGrasse kickin'.
我是《比爾教科學》的比爾·奈
Bill Nye the Science Guy.
美國科學教育家  喜劇演員
《比爾教科學》是他知名的科教節目
比爾  我是尼爾·泰森
Hey, Bill. Neil Tyson.
我們來談兩句
We gotta talk.